Finding Aid for Kenneth P. Davis papers, 1930-1974
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Photographs
  - Cultural treatments
    - Intermediate, thinning, pruning, etc.
      - Miscellaneous (Box 35)
      - Pruning in Western white pine, Idaho (Box 35)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 35)
    - Thinning and establishment of desirable reproduction (Box 35)
  - Fire
    - Burning and replanting (Box 35)
    - Danger stations and instrumentation photos (Box 35)
    - Equipment (Box 35)
    - Handtools (Box 35)
    - Malibu, California (Box 35)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 35)
    - Plows (Box 35)
    - Prescribed burning (Box 35)
    - Views (Box 35)
  - Forest types
    - Japan (Box 35)
    - Southeastern (Box 35)
  - Friends, colleagues, social (Box 35)
  - Georgia Forestry Commission Headquarters 1958 Visit (Box 35)
  - Groups (Box 35)
  - Idaho
    - Magruder Corridor-National Forest Area 1967 (Box 35)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 35)
    - Western white pine, birch, fir, and hemlock (Box 35)
  - Lookout Towers (Box 35)
  - Los Angeles County Forestry Department (Box 35)
  - People and places (Box 35)
  - Places (Box 35)
  - Ponderosa pine and miscellaneous forest types (Box 35)
  - Radiophones in use (U.S. Forestry Department) (Box 35)
  - Sands claim (Box 35)
  - Self (photos of K.P. Davis) (Box 35)
  - Snowshoe Trip, Thunder Bay River, Michigan, Winter 1962 (Box 35)
  - Society of American Foresters (Box 35)
  - Society of American Foresters, Detroit meeting 1965 (Box 35)
  - Southern Spring Trip
    - 1950-1951 (Box 35)
    - 1957 (Box 35)
    - Undated (Box 35)
  - Summer camps, miscellaneous (Box 35)
  - Sylvania Recreation Area Dedication 1967 (Box 35)
  - Thinning experiments, western white pine type (Box 35)
  - Thinning in Western white pine, hemlock, girdling, etc.-Idaho (Box 35)
  - University of Michigan, students (Box 35)
  - Utilization
    - Milling and wood treatment (Box 35)
    - Pulpwood cutting, Ontario (Box 35)
  - Water pumping (Box 35)
  - Western trip undated (Box 35)